[{"answer": "Yeah. Well if you didn't put it in the papers", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " No... Actually, you look more like a cop", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Well... I'll give it a try, Mr. my friend", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Hi, my friend. Did you see the play", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Well? What'd you think", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Sure. Try this acting thing. You can make good money at it", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You don't know what you want", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "No, No arguments. Be my good girl and go. There's a forest, a burning forest, and you know what I have to do", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Oh my friend, my own... my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " Oh, I know that. But it could look more realistic, don't you think", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I'll notice", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Society is falling apart, Miss Farmer, and people have to buckle down, do their jobs. You see, I view myself as the my friend of motion picture industry, and I can't have the fellow who puts on the wheels arguing with the man who installs hea", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " No, I'm concerned with everything", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Yes...", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I don't believe so", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "my friend, you're a movie star now. If you give them what they want, you can get anything", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Some people starve, kid. Until we can do something about it, they might as well see a movie. Makes 'em feel better", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "But I don't want to be like that. I want to do something...", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " Yeah, if I don't make too big an ass of myself", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "It's a perfectly good car. It runs", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I don't care if my clothes are taken seriously. Or my car", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "The speech? Real good", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You got it", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "You think I got it", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Yeah. Yeah, tonight I think I got it", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Hello, my friend", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " Where's my friend", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "A rich actress", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " But... but wait a minute. We're supposed to be different, right? my friend says... This theatre is supposed to be different! And this play... this play is all about what greed and money do to people", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Right now we have to be practical", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "He knows, my friend", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "You wouldn't believe the offers! Just piling in. I mean piling. Some of the best scripts I've read in years", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "my friend? Is she here", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "What's left of my blood", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Help yourself. Everyone else has", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Get your clothes on", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Get your clothes on, lady", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " You have no right! You have no fucking right, you bastards! Get the hell out of here", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "GET OUT", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Have you reported to your Probation Officer as directed", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Did you expect him to look you up", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "I find these initial meetings to be much easier without the concerned relatives in attendance", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Thanks are hardly necessary", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "It's not too late to keep going, up to that place? Be the smartest thing", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "You give up on her", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "What's wrong", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Where are you going", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "I'm sorry, I... I don't have a desk in my room, and...", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "I love you too, my friend", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Where are you going", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "You're not going anywhere", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Be patient, that's all. Take an interest in your treatment and don't dwell on your resentments. You'll be yourself again, I assure you", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "We'll talk more about this. I'll see you later", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "This is it, kid. This is our chance. When you got a chance, you better take it", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "You don't need to screw around anymore. You don't need my friend or Odets or your mother. You need me", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": " Do I go right away or do I have time to take a bath", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "You were hoping for a kind word?! You're my mother! You're supposed to nourish me! Support me", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Fine, thank you. Did you watch the show", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": " How did I look", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Very slow.  But we're not going to stop, are we", "docId": "Frances.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": " No, we're not", "qsentId": 62}]